Guide to the Herman F. Mark Collection RG.002
Poly Archives at the Bern Dibner Library of Science and Technology, NYU Libraries
- Series IV: Publications
  - Subseries G: Monographs and notebooks
    - "Polymer Science Overview: A Tribute to Herman F. Mark" by G. Stahl, 1980 August; cuid2937 (Box 15, Item 18)
    - "The Limits of Science" by P. Medawar, with note to H. Mark, 1984; cuid2938 (Box 15, Item 19)
    - "An Exploration of Patients' Experience in the Recovery Room" by Catherine Mark, 1986; cuid2939 (Box 15, Item 20)
    - "Polymer Pioneers" by P. Morris, 1986; cuid2940 (Box 15, Item 21)
    - "A Career in Composites" by C. Yates, 1988 July; cuid2941 (Box 15, Item 22)
    - "Center of Macromolecular Design for Advanced Technology" A proposal prepared for the Nation Science Foundation, 1988 January 15; cuid2942 (Box 15, Item 23)
    - "Maurits Dekker: A Celebration of a Life 1899-1995" by MDeye, 1995 December; cuid2943 (Box 15, Item 24)
    - "Nucleation and Crystallization of Polymers" Dissertation by Karthigeyan Nagarajan, 2000 January; cuid2944 (Box 15, Item 25)
    - "Erzalungen und Marchen" by Oscar Wilde, undated; cuid2945 (Box 15, Item 26)
    - PINY binder: The Stereo Rubbers, undated; cuid2946 (Box 16, Item 1)
    - PINY binder: Olefin Copolymers, undated; cuid2947 (Box 16, Item 2)
    - PINY binder: Viscoelastic Behavior of Solution Rubbers, undated; cuid2948 (Box 16, Item 3)
    - "Der feste Korper" by R. Sanger, 1938; cuid2949 (Box 16, Item 4)
    - "Langenscheidts Taschenworterbuch" by H. Menge and H. Muller, 1955; cuid2950 (Box 16, Item 5)
    - "Die Hochmolekularen Organischen Verbindungen- Kautschuk und Cellulose" by H. Stauginer, 1960; cuid2951 (Box 16, Item 6)
    - "Frauen" by Gustav Klimt, 1985; cuid2952 (Box 16, Item 7)
    - "Wide Awake at 3 A.M.: By Choice or by Chance" by R. Colman, 1986; cuid2953 (Box 16, Item 8)
    - "Die Gitten der amerikanischen Wilden" by J. Lafitau, 1987; cuid2954 (Box 16, Item 9)
    - "Polymer Science in the Next decade: An International Symposium Honoring Herman F. Mark on his 90th Birthday" ed. by O. Vogl, 1987; cuid2955 (Box 16, Item 10)
    - "From Small Organic Molecules to Large: A Century of Progress: Herman F. Mark" by J. Seeman, 1993; cuid2956 (Box 16, Item 11)
    - "Exploring the Universe with the Hubble Space Telescope" by NASA, undated; cuid2957 (Box 16, Item 12)
    - "From Design to Discovery: Donald J. Cram" Profiles, Pathways, and Dreams ACS series, by Jeffrey Seeman, 1990; cuid2958 (Item 1)
    - "Steriods Made it Possible: Carl Djerassi," Profiles, Pathways, and Dreams ACS series, by Jeffrey Seeman, 1990; cuid2959 (Item 2)
    - "From Cologne to Chapel Hill: Ernest L. Eliel" Profiles, Pathways, and Dreams ACS series, by Jeffrey Seeman, 1990; cuid2960 (Item 3)
    - "Explorations with Sugars: Raymond U. Lemieux" Profiles, Pathways, and Dreams ACS series, by Jeffrey Seeman, 1990; cuid2961 (Item 4)
    - "Some Recollections of Gap Jumping: Sir Derek H. R. Barton" Profiles, Pathways, and Dreams ACS series, by Jeffrey Seeman, 1991; cuid2962 (Item 5)
    - "Enjoying Organic Chemistry, 1927-1987: Egbert Havinga" Profiles, Pathways, and Dreams ACS series, by Jeffrey Seeman, 1991; cuid2963 (Item 6)
    - "A Wandering Natural Products Chemist: Koji Nakanishi" Profiles, Pathways, and Dreams ACS series, by Jeffrey Seeman, 1991; cuid2964 (Item 7)
    - "Seventy Years in Organic Chemistry: Tetsuo Nozoe" Profiles, Pathways, and Dreams ACS series, by Jeffrey Seeman, 1991; cuid2965 (Item 8)
    - "My 132 Semesters of Chemistry Studies: Vladimir Prelog" Profiles, Pathways, and Dreams ACS series, by Jeffrey Seeman, 1991; cuid2966 (Item 9)
    - "Following the Trail of Light: Melvin Calvin," Profiles, Pathways, and Dreams ACS series, by Jeffrey Seeman, 1992; cuid2967 (Item 10)
    - "A Semiempirical Life: Michael J.S. Dewar" Profiles, Pathways, and Dreams ACS series, by Jeffrey Seeman, 1992; cuid2968 (Item 11)
    - "From Small Organic Molecules to Large: A Century of Progress: Herman F. Mark" Profiles, Pathways, and Dreams ACS series, by Jeffrey Seeman, 1993; cuid2969 (Item 12)
    - "To See the Obvious: Arthur J. Birch" Profiles, Pathways, and Dreams ACS series, by Jeffrey Seeman, 1995; cuid2970 (Item 13)
    - "Fifty Years of Free Radicals" Profiles, Pathways, and Dreams ACS series, by Jeffrey Seeman, 1995; cuid2971 (Item 14)
    - "Macromolecular Synthesis," Vol. 7, ed. Edward Fettes, 1979; cuid2972 (Item 15)
    - "Macromolecular Synthesis," Vol. 7, ed. Edward Fettes (copy 2), 1979; cuid2973 (Item 16)
    - "Macromolecular Synthesis," Vol. 8, ed. Eli Pearce, 1982; cuid2974 (Item 17)
    - "Macromolecular Synthesis," Vol. 9, ed. J.A. Moore, 1985; cuid2975 (Item 18)
    - "Macromolecular Synthesis," Vol. 9, ed. J.A. Moore (copy 2), 1985; cuid2976 (Item 19)
    - "Volume I: Materials: State of the Art" Fire Safety Aspects of Polymeric Materials series, 1977; cuid2977 (Item 20)
    - "Volume 2: Test Methods, Specifications, and Standards" Fire Safety Aspects of Polymeric Materials series, 1979; cuid2978 (Item 21)
    - "Volume 2: Test Methods, Specifications, and Standards" Fire Safety Aspects of Polymeric Materials series (copy 2), 1979; cuid2979 (Item 22)
    - "Volume 4: Fire Dynamics and Scenarios" Fire Safety Aspects of Polymeric Materials series, 1978; cuid2980 (Item 23)
    - "Volume 5: Elements of Polymer Fire Safety and Guide to the Designer" Fire Safety Aspects of Polymeric Materials series, 1979; cuid2981 (Item 24)
    - "Volume 6: Aircraft: Civil and Military" Fire Safety Aspects of Polymeric Materials series, 1977; cuid2982 (Item 25)
    - "Volume 7: Buildings" Fire Safety Aspects of Polymeric Materials series, 1979; cuid2983 (Item 26)
    - "Volume 9: Ships" Fire Safety Aspects of Polymeric Materials series, 1980; cuid2984 (Item 27)
    - "Volume 10: Mines and Bunkers" Fire Safety Aspects of Polymeric Materials series, 1980; cuid2985 (Item 28)
    - "High Polymeric Reactions Their Theory and Practice," High Polymers Vol. III, 1941; cuid2986 (Item 29)
    - "Mechanism of Polymer Reactions," High Polymers Vol. III, 1954; cuid2987 (Item 30)
    - "Natural and Synthetic High Polymers," High Polymers Vol. IV, 1942; cuid2988 (Item 31)
    - "Natural and Synthetic High Polymers," High Polymers Vol. IV, Second Edition, 1950; cuid2989 (Item 32)
    - "Cellulose and Cellulose Derivatives" High Polymers Vol. V, 1946; cuid2990 (Item 33)
    - "Cellulose and Cellulose Derivatives" Part I, High Polymers Vol. V, 1954; cuid2991 (Item 34)
    - "Cellulose and Cellulose Derivatives" Part II, High Polymers Vol. V, 1954; cuid2992 (Item 35)
    - "Cellulose and Cellulose Derivatives" Part III, High Polymers Vol. V (2 copies), 1955; cuid2993 (Item 36)
    - "Cellulose and Cellulose Derivatives" Part IV, High Polymers Vol. V (2 copies), 1971; cuid2994 (Item 37)
    - "Cellulose and Cellulose Derivatives" Part V, High Polymers Vol. V (2 copies), 1971; cuid2995 (Item 38)
    - "Phenoplasts: Their Structure, Properties and Chemical Technology," High Polymers VII, 1947; cuid2996 (Item 39)
    - "Emulsion Polymerization" High Polymers Vol. IX, 1955; cuid2997 (Item 40)
    - "Analytical Chemistry of Polymers" Part II, High Polymers Vol. XII, 1962; cuid2998 (Item 41)
    - "Analytical Chemistry of Polymers" Part III, High Polymers Vol. XII, 1962; cuid2999 (Item 42)
    - "Polyethers" Part I, High Polymers Vol. XIII, 1963; cuid3000 (Item 43)
    - "Polyethers" Part III, High Polymers Vol. XIII (2 copies), 1962; cuid3001 (Item 44)
    - "Polymer Chemistry of Synthetic Elastomers" Part I, High Polymers Vol. XXIII, 1968; cuid3002 (Item 45)
    - "Polymer Chemistry of Synthetic Elastomers" Part II, High Polymers Vol. XXIII, 1969; cuid3003 (Item 46)
    - "Vinyl and Diene Monomers" Part 2, High Polymers Vol. XXIV, 1971; cuid3004 (Item 47)
    - "Vinyl and Diene Monomers" Part 3, High Polymers Vol. XXIV (2 copies), 1971; cuid3005 (Item 48)
    - "Cyclic Monomers," High Polymers Vol. XXVI, 1972; cuid3006 (Item 49)
    - "Allyl Compounds and Their Polymers (Including Polyolefins), High Polymers Vol. XXVIII, 1973; cuid3007 (Item 50)
    - "Fracture Processes in Polymeric Solids," ed. Bernard Rosen, 1964; cuid3008 (Item 51)
    - "Proceedings 3rd Annual Conference on the Physics of Compound Semiconductor Interfaces," ed. Mark, 1976; cuid3009 (Item 52)
    - "Proceedings 5th Annual Conference on the Physics of Compound Semiconductor Interfaces," ed. Mark, 1978; cuid3010 (Item 53)
    - "Concepts, Critiques and Comments: Wide and Varied" A Festschrift in Honor of David Rose, 1976; cuid3011 (Item 54)
    - "Selected Papers of Turner Alfrey," ed. R. Boyer and H. Mark, 1986; cuid3012 (Item 55)
    - "Power & Security" by Edward Teller, Hans Mark, and John S. Foster, Jr. (inscribed to the Geheimrath from Hans), 1976; cuid3013 (Item 56)
    - "Crystal Structure and Chemical Constitution: A General Discussion held by the Faraday Society", 1929 March; cuid3014 (Item 57)
    - "Organic Thin Films and Surfaces: Directions for the Nineties" ed. by Abraham Ulman, 1995; cuid3015 (Item 58)
    - "The Blue Nile" by Alan Moorehead, 1962; cuid3016 (Item 59)
    - "Matthews' Textile Fibers" Sixth Edition, ed. by H. R. Mauersberger, 1954; cuid3017 (Item 60)
    - "Natural and Synthetic High Polymers" by K. H. Meyer, 1942; cuid3018 (Item 61)
    - "The Effects of Ionizing Radiation on Natural and Synthetic High Polymers," by Frank Bovey (introduction by Herman Mark), 1958; cuid3019 (Item 62)
    - "Stress-Strain Behavior of Elastic Materials" by O.H. Varga (introduction by Herman Mark and Edmund Immergut), 1966; cuid3020 (Item 63)
    - "Molecular Weight Distributions in Polymers" by Leighton Peebles (introduction by Herman Mark and Edmund Immergut), 1971; cuid3021 (Item 64)
    - "Macromolecular Reviews" Vol. 10, Journal of Polymer Science, ed. A. Peterlin, 1975; cuid3022 (Item 65)
    - "Fiber Structure and Properties," Journal of Applied Polymer Science: Applied Polymer Symposia 33, ed. J.L. White, 1976; cuid3023 (Item 66)
    - "Long-Term Properties of Polymers and Polymeric Materials," Journal of Applied Polymer Science: Applied Polymer Symposia 33, ed. B. Ranby and J.F. Rabek, 1976; cuid3024 (Item 67)
    - "Commodity and Engineering Plastics," Journal of Applied Polymer Science: Applied Polymer Symposia 36, ed. N. Platzer, 1981; cuid3025 (Item 68)
    - "Symposium on Cellulose and Wood as Future Chemical Feedstocks and Sources of Energy, and General Papers," Journal of Applied Polymer Science: Applied Polymer Symposia 37, ed. A Sarko, 1982; cuid3026 (Item 69)
    - "Chemistry and Technology of Rubber," Journal of Applied Polymer Science: Applied Polymer Symposia 39, ed. A. Vidal and J.B. Donnet, 1982; cuid3027 (Item 70)
    - "U.S.-Japan Seminar on Polymer Liquid Crystals," Journal of Applied Polymer Science: Applied Polymer Symposia 41, ed. J.L. White and S. Onogi, 1983; cuid3028 (Item 71)
    - "Advances in Preparation and Charaterization of Multiphase Polymer Systems," Journal of Applied Polymer Science: Applied Polymer Symposia 60, ed. R.J. Ambrose and S.L. Aggarwal, 1977; cuid3029 (Item 72)
    - "Unsolved Problems of Co- and Graft Polymerization," Journal of Applied Polymer Science: Applied Polymer Symposia 64, ed. O. Vogl and C.I. Simionescu, 1976; cuid3030 (Item 73)
    - "Microcalorimetry of Macromolecules," Journal of Applied Polymer Science: Applied Polymer Symposia 69, ed. B. Sedlacek, C.G. Overberger, H.F. Mark, 1979; cuid3031 (Item 74)
    - "Polymers with Unusual Properties," Journal of Applied Polymer Science: Applied Polymer Symposia 70, ed. C.W. Allen, 1982; cuid3032 (Item 75)
    - "High Temperature and Flame-Resistant Fibers," Journal of Applied Polymer Science: Applied Polymer Symposia 20, ed. J. Preston and J. Economy, 1973; cuid3033 (Item 76)
    - "Luminescence from Biological and Synthetic Macromolecules Eighth Katzir Conference," ed. H. Morawetz and I.Z. Steinberg, 1981; cuid3034 (Item 77)
    - "Handbook of Fiber Science and Technology: Volume I," ed. M. Lewin and S.B. Sello, 1983; cuid3035 (Item 78)
    - "Handbook of Fiber Science and Technology: Volume II," ed. M. Lewin and S.B. Sello, 1983; cuid3036 (Item 79)
    - "Polymer Characterization," ed. B.J. Hunt and M.I. james, 1993; cuid3037 (Item 80)
    - "Free-Radical Polymerisation," ed. C.H. Bamford and C.F.H. Tipper, 1976; cuid3038 (Item 81)
    - "Monomeric Acrylic Esters," by E.H. Riddle, 1954; cuid3039 (Item 82)
    - "Handbook of Composite Reinforcements," ed. S.M. Lee, 1993; cuid3040 (Item 83)
    - "Elementary Crystallography," by M.J. Buerger, 1956; cuid3041 (Item 84)
    - "Journal of Polymer Science," Vol. 51, No. 156, 1961 June; cuid3042 (Item 85)
    - "Proceedings of the Robert A. Welch Foundation 39th Conference on Chemical Research Nanophase Chemistry", 1995; cuid3043 (Item 86)
    - "Theorie und Molekulare Deutung Technologischer Eigenschaften von Hochpolymeren Werkstoffen", 1956; cuid3044 (Item 87)
    - "Forty Years of Firsts: The Recollections of a Dow Corning Pioneer," E.L. Warrick, 1990; cuid3045 (Item 88)
    - "Fracture Processes in Polymeric Solids," ed. Bernard Rosen, 1964; cuid3046 (Item 89)
    - "Handbook of Organic Coatings: A Comprehensive Guide for the Coatings Industry," by Raymond Seymour and Herman Mark, 1990; cuid3047 (Item 90)
    - "Metal and Metalloid Amides: Syntheses, Structures, and Physical and Chemical Properties, 1980; cuid3048 (Item 91)
    - "Multicomponent Polymer Systems," ed., I.S. Miles and S. Rostami, 1992; cuid3049 (Item 92)
    - "Infrared Spectroscopy of Polymer Blends, Composites and Surfaces," by Andrew Garton, 1992 November 19; cuid3050 (Item 93)
    - "Rheology of Polymers," by G.V. Vinogradov and A.Ya. Malkin, 1979; cuid3051 (Item 94)
    - "Giant Molecules," by Herman Mark (4 copies), 1966; cuid3052 (Item 95)
    - "Stereospecific Catalysis and Stereoregular Addition Polymers Volume II" A Collection of the Original Papers by Prof. Guilio Natta and coworkers, circa 1958; cuid3053 (Item 96)
    - "Stereospecific Catalysis and Stereoregular Addition Polymers Volume III" A Collection of the Original Papers by Prof. Guilio Natta and coworkers, circa 1959; cuid3054 (Item 97)
    - "Stereospecific Catalysis and Stereoregular Addition Polymers Volume IV" A Collection of the Original Papers by Prof. Guilio Natta and coworkers, circa 1959; cuid3055 (Item 98)
    - Kaiser-Wilhelm-Institut fur Faserstoffchemic, undated; cuid3056 (Item 99)
    - Polymer Science: Series A Chemistry Physics, Vol. 41 no. 12, 1999 December; cuid3057 (Item 100)
    - "Nieder Osterriech", 1979; cuid3058 (Item 101)
    - "Textile Fibres under the X-rays" by W.T. Astbury, circa 1943; cuid3059 (Item 102)
    - "Mechanical Properties of Wood and Paper" ed. R. Meredith, 1953; cuid3060 (Item 103)
    - "Die physik der Hochpolymeren" by H.A. Stuart, 1955; cuid3061 (Item 104)
    - "Direct Use of the Sun's Energy" by Farrington Daniels, 1964; cuid3062 (Item 105)
    - "Progress in the Chemistry of Organic Natural Products" ed. L. Zechmeister, 1953; cuid3063 (Item 106)
    - "Partners in Progress: A Chapter in the American-Swedish Exchange of Knowledge" ed. A Kastrup and N.W. Olsson, 1977; cuid3064 (Item 107)
    - "Grundriss der Makromolekularen Chemic" by B. Vollmert, 1962; cuid3065 (Item 108)
    - "New Commercial Polymer 1969-1975" by H-G Elias, 1977; cuid3066 (Item 109)
    - "The Chain Photon Theory of matter and Energy" by R.L. Saxe, 1977; cuid3067 (Item 110)
    - "Progress in Polymer Science Japan: Volume 7" ed. T. Otsu, 1974; cuid3068 (Item 111)
    - "Lehrbuch der Theoretischen Physik" by G. Joos, 1934; cuid3069 (Item 112)
- Series V: Subject files
  Arrangement
  These files were in a vertical file cabinet, which was moved from Professor Mark's office to Dibner Library some time in the 1990s. The cabinet contained two sets of alphabetized files, and although there is much overlap between the file names and date ranges between these two sets, Professor Mark's original order is maintained as two sets with the original dividers.
  - Subseries A: Green tab dividers, 1989-1992
    - A, 1990-1991; cuid3070 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - ACS, 1990-1991; cuid3071 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Aloma Chair, 1990-1991; cuid3072 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Applicants, 1992; cuid3073 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Bauer house, 1990; cuid3074 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - C, 1990-1991; cuid3075 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Contributions, 1990; cuid3076 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Library Contributions, 1991; cuid3077 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - D, 1991-1992; cuid3078 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - E, 1991; cuid3079 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - F, 1990-1991; cuid3080 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Felsinger, 1990-1992; cuid3081 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - G, 1990-1991; cuid3082 (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Gordon Conference, 1991; cuid3083 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - Greve, 1990-1992; cuid3084 (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - H, 1990-1991; cuid3085 (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - I, 1990-1991; cuid3086 (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - Isovolta, 1990; cuid3087 (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - Interscience, 1990-1992; cuid3088 (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - J, 1991; cuid3089 (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - Jelling, 1990-1991; cuid3090 (Box 17, Folder 21)
    - K, 1991; cuid3091 (Box 17, Folder 22)
    - Kiser, 1991-1992; cuid3092 (Box 17, Folder 23)
    - L, 1990-1992; cuid3093 (Box 17, Folder 24)
    - Leydig, 1991; cuid3094 (Box 17, Folder 25)
    - LORD, 1991-1992; cuid3095 (Box 17, Folder 26)
    - Mc, 1991; cuid3096 (Box 17, Folder 27)
    - M, 1991-1992; cuid3097 (Box 17, Folder 28)
    - Hans Mark- National Academy, 1991; cuid3098 (Box 17, Folder 29)
    - Mail Service, 1991; cuid3099 (Box 17, Folder 30)
    - N, 1991-1992; cuid3100 (Box 17, Folder 31)
    - Nominations, 1989-1991; cuid3101 (Box 17, Folder 32)
    - Novophalt, 1991; cuid3102 (Box 17, Folder 33)
    - N.A.S., 1988-1992; cuid3103 (Box 17, Folder 34)
    - National Patent, 1991; cuid3104 (Box 17, Folder 35)
    - Nominations, 1987; cuid3105 (Box 17, Folder 36)
    - O, 1990-1991; cuid3106 (Box 17, Folder 37)
    - Overberger, 1991; cuid3107 (Box 17, Folder 38)
    - Orders, undated; cuid3108 (Box 17, Folder 39)
    - OMV, 1992; cuid3109 (Box 17, Folder 40)
    - P, 1990-1991; cuid3110 (Box 17, Folder 41)
    - E. Pearce- Education Award, 1991; cuid3111 (Box 17, Folder 42)
    - Pearce-Flory Award, 1989; cuid3112 (Box 17, Folder 43)
    - Poly, 1991-1992; cuid3113 (Box 17, Folder 44)
    - Poly President, 1991; cuid3114 (Box 17, Folder 45)
    - Publications, 1991; cuid3115 (Box 17, Folder 46)
    - Programs, 1991; cuid3116 (Box 17, Folder 47)
    - Positions, 1990; cuid3117 (Box 17, Folder 48)
    - Poly President Search, 1991; cuid3118 (Box 17, Folder 49)
    - Patents, 1991; cuid3119 (Box 17, Folder 50)
    - Petrovicki, 1990-1992; cuid3120 (Box 17, Folder 51)
    - R, 1991; cuid3121 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Reports, 1959-1966; cuid3122 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Recommendations, 1990-1991; cuid3123 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - S, 1990-1991; cuid3124 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Soviet, 1991; cuid3125 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Slides, undated; cuid3126 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - T, 1990-1991; cuid3127 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Thesis- Foreign, 1991-1992; cuid3128 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - U, 1991; cuid3129 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - V, 1991-1992; cuid3130 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Visitors, 1991; cuid3131 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - W, 1990-1992; cuid3132 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Weizmann, 1990-1992; cuid3133 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - XYZ, 1991-1992; cuid3134 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Subseries B: Beige tab dividers, 1979-1991; 1989-1991
    - A, 1989-1990; cuid3135 (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Abstracts, undated; cuid3136 (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - Abstracts [lectures], undated; cuid3137 (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - ACS, 1988-1990; cuid3138 (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - Applicants, 1988-1990; cuid3139 (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - Alsted-LORD-Mark, 1989-1991; cuid3140 (Box 18, Folder 20)
    - B, 1990; cuid3141 (Box 18, Folder 21)
    - Bauer House, 1990; cuid3142 (Box 18, Folder 22)
    - Bower Award, 1990; cuid3143 (Box 18, Folder 23)
    - C, 1989-1990; cuid3144 (Box 18, Folder 24)
    - Contributions, 1989-1990; cuid3145 (Box 18, Folder 25)
    - D, 1989-1990; cuid3146 (Box 18, Folder 26)
    - Donations, 1990; cuid3147 (Box 18, Folder 27)
    - Drafts, undated; cuid3148 (Box 18, Folder 28)
    - Dues, 1990; cuid3149 (Box 18, Folder 29)
    - E, 1990; cuid3150 (Box 18, Folder 30)
    - F, 1990; cuid3151 (Box 18, Folder 31)
    - Franklin Institute, 1990; cuid3152 (Box 18, Folder 32)
    - Felsinger, 1990; cuid3153 (Box 18, Folder 33)
    - G, 1990; cuid3154 (Box 18, Folder 34)
    - Greve Foundation, 1990; cuid3155 (Box 18, Folder 35)
    - H, 1989-1990; cuid3156 (Box 18, Folder 36)
    - Harvey Prize, 1990; cuid3157 (Box 18, Folder 37)
    - I, 1989-1990; cuid3158 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Isovolta, 1989-1990; cuid3159 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Interscience, 1990-1991; cuid3160 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - J, 1990; cuid3161 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Jelling, 1989-1990; cuid3162 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Kiser, 1990; cuid3163 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Kricheldorf Correspondence, 1991; cuid3164 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - L, 1990; cuid3165 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Leydig, 1989-1990; cuid3166 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Lists, 1990; cuid3167 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - LORD, 1990; cuid3168 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - M, 1990; cuid3169 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - MMSO [Miscellaneous slides], undated; cuid3170 (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - N, 1990; cuid3171 (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - National Academy, 1987-1990; cuid3172 (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - National patent, 1990; cuid3173 (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - Nominations, 1990; cuid3174 (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - Novophalt, 1989-1990; cuid3175 (Box 19, Folder 18)
    - Overberger, 1988-1990; cuid3176 (Box 19, Folder 19)
    - P, 1989-1990; cuid3177 (Box 19, Folder 20)
    - Perkin Medal, 1979-1980; cuid3178 (Box 19, Folder 21)
    - Programs, 1990; cuid3179 (Box 19, Folder 22)
    - Poly, 1990; cuid3180 (Box 19, Folder 23)
    - Poly-President, 1990; cuid3181 (Box 19, Folder 24)
    - Publications, 1990; cuid3182 (Box 19, Folder 25)
    - Polymer Science, 1976-2003; cuid3183 (Box 19, Folder 26)
    - R, 1989-1990; cuid3184 (Box 19, Folder 27)
    - Recommendations, 1990; cuid3185 (Box 19, Folder 28)
    - Resumes, undated; cuid3186 (Box 19, Folder 29)
    - Reports, undated; cuid3187 (Box 19, Folder 30)
    - Research Programs, 1960s; cuid3188 (Box 19, Folder 31)
    - Royalties, 1989; cuid3189 (Box 19, Folder 32)
    - S, 1989-1990; cuid3190 (Box 19, Folder 33)
    - Seeman Story, 1988-1989; cuid3191 (Box 19, Folder 34)
    - Seeman, Jeffrey, 1990; cuid3192 (Box 19, Folder 35)
    - Soviet Academy, 1990; cuid3193 (Box 19, Folder 36)
    - T, 1990; cuid3194 (Box 19, Folder 36)
    - Thesis- Foreign, 1990; cuid3195 (Box 19, Folder 37)
    - U, 1990; cuid3196 (Box 19, Folder 38)
    - V, 1990; cuid3197 (Box 19, Folder 39)
    - Visitors, 1990; cuid3198 (Box 19, Folder 40)
    - W, 1990; cuid3199 (Box 19, Folder 41)
    - Weizmann Institute, 1990; cuid3200 (Box 19, Folder 42)
    - XYZ, 1990; cuid3201 (Box 19, Folder 43)
    - February, 1989; cuid3202 (Box 19, Folder 44)
    - March, 1990; cuid3203 (Box 19, Folder 45)
    - May, 1989-1990; cuid3204 (Box 19, Folder 46)
    - July, 1990; cuid3205 (Box 19, Folder 47)
    - August, 1990; cuid3206 (Box 19, Folder 48)
    - September, 1990; cuid3207 (Box 19, Folder 49)
    - November, 1990; cuid3208 (Box 19, Folder 50)
- Series VI: Polytechnic Institute of Brooklyn and the Polymer Research Institute
  - Subseries A: Mark Birthday Symposia and Festschrift
    Scope and Contents
    Professor Mark received birthday letters, cards, and festschrift from Europe, Asia, North America, South America, and the Middle East. Notable well-wishers include President Ronald Reagan, Mayor Ed Koch, and Polytechnic's Bern Dibner.
    - 60th Birthday Symposium, 1955-1995; cuid3209 (Box 20, Folder 1)